Hard pass.
Eh?
What do you mean, hard pass?
Your stats are way too low.
I'm not interested in babysitting a couple of noobs.
Hey! What did you just call me?
We're both still working hard to level up.
Once we get stronger, we can help you out.
And yet you couldn't even tell that Father Zombie was undead.
That's like basic awareness.
You guys are pretty useless.
I don't need dead weight tagging along.
Then I'd better show you what I'm made of!
They call me Mosh the Hero back in my hometown of Nakashi!
Whatevs. Sounds like a crock-o-she.
That's Nakashi, jerk!
That's it, I'm not going to be you!
Hey, what's going on over here?
Who would dare to desecrate this holy church into ruin?
No, sister, are you hurt?
You, explain yourselves.
If I sense deception, I'll haul you in for interrogation.
This is a misunderstanding. I can tell you how it all broke down.
Oh, wait, too soon?
The truth is, there was a horrible creature that disguised itself as a priest.
Were they responsible for the sinful misdeed?
I'm still rather shaken, so the exact details are vague.
But yes, I'm positive it was that undead brute who destroyed the chapel.
One thing I do remember clearly, it said 10,000 more of its ungodly ilk would come to join it.
10,000?
Already overtaken Crane Castle heading south.
Who could have imagined such numbers?
Hold fast to your faith, sir.
You see, God has not forsaken us yet.
Don't you worry.
After all, the heavens have sent us a divine goddess,
as well as a blessed hero with great strength,
and two allies with dragonkin blood in their veins.
Please forgive my rudeness.
Let's start over.
We're knights of the Empire, sent to defend Seymour,
sworn to defeat the Undead Horde.
Sir Hero, we humbly request that you fight alongside us.
How much you got?
How much? Of what?
Duh, how much money.
Hold on, Seiya.
You think now is the best time for this?
Pipe down.
I learned a new move recently.
It's one that requires a fairly hefty amount of capital.
Capital?
What kind of scammy technique are we talking here?
Of course.
You'll be compensated with a handsome reward.
At least a thousand gold coins.
Cool, bro.
I'll just need that in writing.
One moment.
There's 200 knights on their way here.
Don't you want our help?
We're the Imperial-
Hard pass.
What do you mean, hard pass?
I'll bet this town has a few stragglers lurking around.
You guys should stay here and protect them.
Yo, are you paying attention, mashed potato?
Hey, my name is Mosh the Hero.
Stop mispronouncing everything!
If you're not going back to Krakoshi,
then help out the knights.
Or whatever isn't around me.
Well, what do we do now?
Ha!
Definitely not whatever that jerk says!
Huh?
Where are you going?
Slow down!
Guys, don't go!
MASH!
Hey, Lulu!
Oh, boy.
I hope they aren't planning to bum-rush a horde of brain-eaters.
I doubt they're that stupid.
But even so, I'll have wiped out those dead gas bags first.
Okay, so you may be ridiculously strong,
but seriously,
should we all just work together?
No way.
That's dumb.
Oh, excuse me for thinking a little teamwork might be a good idea.
There are 10,000 zombies.
Having another one or 200 people with us is pointless.
No need for anyone else to die,
including those annoying kids from Fava Bean.
This is new.
Is he showing concern for the children?
Say-ya!
Oh!
What?
When'd you get up there?
I'm heading off.
Go wait at the inn.
Huh?
What did you say?
And in case you think I need your help,
the answer's still hard pass.
Ah!
Oh, Lulu!
Did he reject me when I'm a literal goddess?
Wait, is this a dream?
Hard pass!
That lousy, ungrateful, selfish, glory-hugging meathead!
You're done-zo!
Ooh!
I'm gonna hard pass you!
Ah!
Order!
Grant it to the goddess Restarté
the gift of fight she should already have!
This is the privilege to unlock sublime abilities
in desperate times when heroes need our support.
An order!
A special measure of the divine realm!
Looking good, if I do say so myself.
I'll get you and your little abs, too.
Rista Wing!
Never underestimate a goddess!
This is starting to get old.
Time to go full throttle.
Hey, no fair!
Moisting Force Megamite Power!
I gotta direct all my mojo into my wings!
Ew!
Oh my god, it's the pain!
My port flappers!
Come on, Restarté!
You gotta dig deep!
You can do it!
Put your wings into it!
Looks like special measures of the divine realm
aren't so special, huh?
Such a princess, honestly.
Come on, let's go.
Huh?
Wow, he's such a gentleman.
He's even holding my hand.
It feels like we're on a date.
Hey, Rista.
Yes, what is it?
My name?
Not the usual hey or hey you.
Oh, you rascal.
Inner celestial love is forbidden.
But I won't tell if you won't.
Wait.
We could totally be making out right now.
What the crap?
I'm just gonna go for it.
I think we need to speed it up.
What?
I thought it was a goner.
You always forget that you're immortal.
Funny, though.
You sure look dead to me.
And whose fault do you think that is?
I've got both butts on my beautiful wings.
I look like I've been molting.
Can't you fix them with your fancy pants healing magic?
Anyway, shut your face, Hole.
We don't want any unexpected company.
So they're marching as one to show the Demon Lord's power.
It's kind of impressive.
So to be on the safe side, I'll break them up before they get too far.
They won't survive my bombardment.
From what bombs, though?
Rockets and missiles don't exist in Gaea Brande.
Good thing I've learned a skill to replace them.
Huh?
With what exactly?
Hush, and I'll show you.
What the...
You're kidding me!
Who hurt you?
The meteor strike.
It's on the smaller side, but if it falls at a sufficiently high speed, the collision will be catastrophic.
Pure annihilation.
I kicked up the energy towards the end.
The moment it made impact, it became superheated and vaporized, resulting in an explosion.
Of course, yeah.
Oh, although it's very powerful, it's still a technique with considerable limits.
I can only use it in the open, and it takes a while to cast.
So, at what point did I miss you learning to apocalypse?
When I was in the divine realm, while making poop skirt cry.
Of course, how could I forget you were supposed to be studying sword moves, not torturing the guy.
Well, I think that took out most of them, but I'm not done.
Not until I launch another meteor first.
Awesome.
Talk about gains.
That's strong enough to take out a heavenly king like Deathmogla for sure.
Nothing against Mash and Elulu.
But this boy can do bad all by himself.
All he has to do is make that happen at the Demon Lord's castle, and then our job is done.
Piece of cake.
What happened? Are you all right?
I may have gone too hardcore.
I need to recover for a while.
I got you, hero.
Let's head back to town and get you to the inn right away.
He fired off two of those spells in a row.
I must have eaten up most of his MP.
I started out with 15,000 MP.
There's just 13,000 left.
Huh?
You barely used any of it, you hoarder!
Mash disappeared on you?
Yes. He went missing two days ago, and I still can't find him anywhere.
Maybe he went back home to your village.
That's what worries me. He would have told me first.
I'm sure he's doing fine.
The chances are slim to none that he'll run into any real trouble.
Especially now that the undead baddies are gone.
It's because of that hero. Isn't he cool?
I wouldn't go that far.
He won't stop nerding out over this new synthesis skill.
He's spent his reward on new weapons and armor.
And now he's a shut-in.
He's probably tinkering away in his quarters.
Let's strap by and see what he's up to.
Sayah! I'm coming in!
What is this mess?
Rista.
Come check this out.
A platinum sword!
That's amazing!
What'd you do to make this thing?
Combining swords on their own didn't improve their strength by much.
To forge a mighty weapon, I needed something unique.
And then, I found a special catalyst.
So what did you use?
Blonde goddess hair.
What?
I found some in your room, because you shed like an old dying dog.
A little this, a little synthesizing it with a steel blade.
And boom, you're welcome.
Wow. A lot of questions right now.
But I'm glad you found some part of me so useful.
Hold on to that for me.
Also, I need more hair.
Like a lot.
You can borrow my razor.
Do not use the sword.
Shut up!
I've got a special delivery for a hero.
What is that?
Who sent it here?
A strange man wearing a hood brought it over.
He said something about wanting to give that meathead hero a gift.
That sounds fishy.
Could be an explosive.
You open it.
Just because I can't die doesn't mean you can explosive boss me.
Oh my.
That's that sexy little vixen.
I don't like it anymore!
No, this is bad!
Ash is in trouble!
Hello.
Can you see me?
Do you hear the sound of my voice?
Well, I can see you all perfectly from here.
I spy a strappingly handsome hero, a beautiful goddess in white, and an adorable young red-haired girl.
A peculiar mirror, is it not?
It can reveal images from far away through the magic of the demon lord.
Oh, I've yet to introduce myself.
My name is Death Magma.
I'm one of the four heavenly kings, and my unique specialty is necromancy, of course.
Oh, that's the undead general?
Well, what kind of general doesn't march with his army?
I must admit, I didn't expect you to dispatch my minions so easily.
Luckily, I was able to command them remotely.
Speaking of that, do you know how long it takes to build a legion of undead soldiers?
Obviously, I thought I'd offset my losses with revenge.
With this weak, milk-smelling boy.
No, stop it!
Leave him alone!
Working with corpses is tedious, but playing with a life is so much fun.
And when that gets boring, there's always murder.
No, don't touch him!
Please!
That's enough, you monster!
Oh my, I'm begging for your life at the end.
Go right ahead and cry as much as you'd like.
Hey, Hiro, I heard you took out all 10,000 of those zombies.
You're a big meathead that's full of himself, but you're the real deal.
You're just different, you know?
So please, no matter what happens, you've got to save the world.
That poor boy.
Come on, that didn't sound like crying at all!
Fortunately, we won't have to endure any of your baby-blathering for much longer.
Somebody do something!
I'm begging you to save him, please!
Beg all you want!
Your hero can't save him.
All you can do is watch as I slice through his neck.
Rista, open a portal to the Divine Realm.
But, even if time is faster there compared to Gaya Brande, what could we possibly do?
Just open it, now.
If you say so.
I have to say, Mosh, you don't totally suck.
Once we get you out of there, I'm gonna let you carry my gear for me.
Ah!
You see, I've already been here before.
Since then, I've been running simulations again and again.
What if I had less time?
What would I do then?
Ha!
Do you not understand we aren't even in the same room?
You stupid meathead!
You can't touch me!
Stop it!
Hm.
Ah!
No!
But how?
Photon swords can cut the fabric of space, bro.
Meet my dimension blade.
According to what laws that thing is excessive?
Hurry up.
The real battle's just begun.
Huh?
Care to explain?
We managed to confuse him momentarily.
But once he loses it, he's gonna kill Mosh.
Right.
So what's the plan?
As you know, time flows much faster in the Divine Realm than it does back there.
It won't take Triclops more than 10 seconds to find a weapon and shank Dragon Boy with it.
Therefore, we have less than 15 minutes to figure out how to get to them first and rescue our guy.
Okay, I think I got it.
I might know someone who can help, but let me lead.
You just need to stay quiet.
Granny, are you the head goddess around here?
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to shut your mouth?
Sorry, Ishtar.
So sorry.
I really mean it.
I'm looking for shrooms on Gaya Brandy, and it's urgent.
Bust out a portal.
That is not how you speak to a great goddess!
And no more fungus puns!
His name is Mosh!
So, in other words, you're saying you'd like me to help you find your companion.
But Divine Law forbids goddesses from granting any excessive support to humankind.
All you'd be doing is making a hole, adorn a specific spot like this chick does all the time.
Tot's no big.
True, true.
I do believe you might just have a point there.
Very well, then.
Ah, there it is.
They're in the forest near Crane Castle.
Your friend is being held captive in a vast dungeon.
Thanks, you're always incredible, Ishtar.
Good.
Now drop us in.
Right in front of the mashed potato.
Okay.
Great, now we're doing potatoes.
Thank you for helping us.
We'd be lost without your aid.
Come on, say something!
Hey, good job.
Thanks, Meemaw.
Can you not be smug for five seconds?
Ah!
Do you even know what you're walking us into?
Duh, what do you take me for?
As soon as we exit the portal, I'm hitting him with Hell's Fire.
While he's distracted, you can use the moment to scoop up Mosh.
Let's go.
Ah, voucher that.
It's impressive how much you've grown, Mr. Seiya Ryuguin.
I bid you good hunting.
Ah, it hurts!
My hand!
But how?
Miss me?
Hell's Fire!
Hey, it's Rista.
You okay?
I think so.
Oh, how heartless.
Let's get you patched up.
How's he doing?
Black flames.
It looks like the fire is protecting him.
What kind of monster is that?
It's...
It's a...
Is that all it took to take down Chaos Machina?
Because it won't work on this Heavenly King.
Your weakness is insulting!
Is that a ghost monster?
I already tried that stuff.
It didn't work.
Well, right.
I bet that was your first move.
Hold up.
So it's not a ghost?
This one's name is Dark Virus.
The mightiest, fiercest creature I've ever created out of my hundreds of experiments.
A fire type?
I thought you only created the undead!
Modifying all manner of monsters just so happens to be my special skill, you basic symbol, then!
Who you call a basic?
We need to exploit his weaknesses!
Defense is over a hundred thousand?
He's immune to all weapon attacks?
Only weak against ice magic.
Yes, you blunt idiot.
You fight it by disrupting its molecular structure with the oscillatory wave skill.
Cold attacks will convert its affiliation from fire to ice, making its ghostly body materialize.
If you can hit Dark Virus with a power that's greater than its defense, only then can you defeat it.
Huh.
Thanks for the boss walkthrough, Pops.
Hold on.
Oscillatory wave is a melee-only technique, and ice spells are the complete opposite of Seiya's fire magic.
There's no way to beat him!
I fed you bits of hope so I could savor every moment of your despair.
I have hypothesized every contingency and planned accordingly, for that's the genius of a true tactician.
Is this really happening?
Pretty much!
How surprising.
I'm kind of shocked, honestly.
You say you've done a lot of hypothesizing and planning?
Nah.
You act so pretentious, but I can read you like an open book.
Are you implying you've somehow anticipated this exact situation?
I'm implying you're a huge tool and you've already lost and don't know it.
Nice talk, Sugar Lips, but you won't defeat him.
He's invincible, and you're a sad excuse for an unprepared hero.
That's not my style.
I am perfectly prepared.
I'm 100% ready for this fight.
I'm ready to wipe that smug look off your dumb emo face!
I'm ready to go!
Wait, what?
Behold, a fire that won't burn out until it consumes you!
Dodge if you wish, but everyone behind you will perish instead!
Ugh, that means us!
Don't need to dodge you.
Go ahead and do your worst.
You still dare to attack me?
Duh!
That's impossible! You're a swordsman! How do you have a melee skill?
I don't believe in limiting myself. If I couldn't use my blade, then I'd have to use my fists.
Some enemies are resistant to sword attacks, and there's no telling when it might break during combat.
What if it got stolen by my opponents? Or what if it got rusted, or dissolved, or got eaten by moths?
It's a good thing I learned hand-to-hand combat.
Okay, that is unbelievably cautious.
Doesn't matter! Because you're still no match for Dark Virus and his burning fists of fiery death!
You think you can counter with your puny human hands? Your whole arm will explode!
Wait, what is happening? Fire and ice magic are incompatible! There's no way you should be able to use both!
That amulet!
An item that grabs the properties of ice?!
That's it! Even if he can't produce it on his own, he can achieve the same effect!
Wait, where did he find something like that to begin with?
Synthesis! You made that bracelet yourself!
Yeah.
Nice! But what did you synthesize to make that?
I just used an ordinary bangle, a few ice cubes, and your hair.
Yeah, your hair made it work.
Huh?
Oh, there's more where that came from.
Some for lightning, some for light, some for dark, and of course the list goes on. I made spares too.
And yes, all of them synthesized from hairs that were scattered around your bedroom.
That's a lot of hair! Oh my gosh, I'm not going bald, am I?
Only his body materialized! You and your stupid hair still can't overcome Dark Virus' defenses!
You're right. Unfortunately, I don't. But it's no problem.
You know what's effective against a vulnerable, glistening body of ice?
A flame attack.
Oh, they didn't think of that! Dark Virus, close in and stop his attack!
It's too late.
A white-hot fixed-point strike. Phoenix thrust!
Thrustin' it!
Is he for real? He just demolished that behemoth like it was nothing.
Eat it, sucker! That's a one in a hundred million phenomenon over there!
No, no, no! There's no way!
That's what you get for monologuing yourself, you loser!
Well, if he hadn't told us how to win, I'm sure I would have found out soon enough.
Yeah, I believe you, because you're the smartest and strongest hero ever!
Now then, it's time for me to finish taking out the trash.
After that, this room needs a deep clean.
You go right ahead! Take all the time you need, okay?
Ah!
教えて!
心の在り方ステータスを
強さも不器用さも
君は特別すぎたよ
魔法だって
解けない謎の横顔で
見つめた明日はぐれ星を巡るの
何度目サプライジング
嫌だねどこ行くの
ここではぐれたらノーマレーン
離さないであなたへお願いは一個だけ
Be Perfect Please Be Perfect Please
未来はきっと繋いだ糸
遠く細いけど輝いは絆
確かめた追いつけない
オラバラスライン
刻んでそっと痛いな一歩
愛想のない大きな手のひら
心配のプリズムなど
独り 愛のために
世界の鍵 本当の勇気は
In your hand 抱きしめるよ